{
    "id": "21ef93e9a67844d19aa1d06b3107ad2a",
    "title": "Past simple and past continuous: grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "7e4a7f60a2f64ac696d552a377361d86",
            "title": "Past Simple And Past Continuous Tense Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When I ................................. to work, I .............................. Peter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "drove, saw",
                        "was driving, saw",
                        "drove, was seeing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "When I ........................................ a bath, the telephone ......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was having, rang",
                        "had, was ringing",
                        "was having, was ringing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ........................................ when someone knocked on the door.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was sleeping",
                        "slept",
                        "am sleeping"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "While she ...................................... games, I .........................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was playing, was working",
                        "played, worked",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "As I ............................... my eyes, I ................................... a strange sight.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "opened, saw",
                        "was opening, was seeing",
                        "was opening, saw"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "James ..................................... the lounge while I .............................. supper.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "tidied, cooked",
                        "was tidying, cooked",
                        "tidied, was cooking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "While they ....................................... caroms somebody ........................................ into the house.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "were playing, broke",
                        "played, broke",
                        "were playing, was breaking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ...................................... of it just when you ..................................... your mouth.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "thought, opened",
                        "was thinking, were opening",
                        "thought, were opening"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "When she ......................................... a bath, the child ................................. to cry.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was having, began",
                        "had, was beginning",
                        "was having, was beginning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She took out her pen and .......................................... writing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "started",
                        "was starting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}